http://www.wincatalog.com/terms-of-use-and-privacy-policy.html#cookies

General Information
WinCatalog.com provides both free and non-free (evaluation) software. By downloading it or using WinCatalog.com web site, you agree to the following terms of use and privacy policy listed below.
By downloading non-free software from this web site, you start a free but limited evaluation period. After reaching this limit (or earlier when you ensure that the software suits your needs), you may purchase an official license to remove all limitations.
Copyright
WinCatalog.com: the trade name under which OrangeCat Software, LLC provides the software and the service on this web site.
The information on this Web site is protected by copyright:
Copyright © 2001-2020 WinCatalog.com All Rights Reserved.
Except as specifically permitted herein, no portion of the information on this Web site may be reproduced in any form or by any means without prior written permission from WinCatalog.com.
Use of Software
Software and accompanying documentation that are made available to download from this Web site are the copyrighted work of WinCatalog.com and/or its affiliates or licensors.
Use of the software is governed by the terms of the applicable license agreement, which accompanies or is included with such software.
If you do not agree to these terms, you are not authorized to use the software.
Use of Web Site Information
Unless otherwise indicated elsewhere on this Web site, you may view, copy, print, and distribute materials (text, images) available on this Web site subject to the following conditions:
The materials may be used solely for personal, informational, non-commercial and internal purposes;
The materials may not be modified or altered in any way;
Any copy of the materials or portion thereof must include the copyright notice above as well as the following:
Visible and clicable link to the main page of this web site (https://www.wincatalog.com) or directly to a page of this web site where the materials are originally located.
The following statement: "This material may be used solely for personal, informational, non-commercial and internal purposes."
WinCatalog.com reserves the right to revoke such authorization at any time, and any such use shall be discontinued immediately upon written notice from WinCatalog.com.
The rights granted herein to view, copy, print, and distribute the materials does not include the design or layout of this Web site. Elements of this Web site are protected by trade dress and other laws and may not be copied or imitated in whole or in part.
DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS
This section is extremely important. Please read it carefully.
TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE SERVICES DATA AND
INFORMATION ARE PROVIDED ENTIRELY “AS IS”, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY
WHATSOEVER, AND ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED,
INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON INFRINGEMENT, ARE HEREBYEXPRESSLY
DISCLAIMED, AND THE USER HEREBY WAIVES ALL SUCH WARRANTIES.
NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, THE USER OBTAINS
FROM WINCATALOG.COM OR ORANGECAT SOFTWARE, LLC OR THROUGH OR FROM THE
SOFTWARE OR SERVICE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN
THESE TERMS OF USE.
THIS WEB SITE COULD INCLUDE TECHNICAL OR OTHER INACCURACIES OR
TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE
INFORMATION HEREIN; THESE CHANGES WILL BE INCORPORATED IN NEW
EDITIONS OF THIS WEB SITE. WINCATALOG.COM MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS
AND/OR CHANGES IN THE PRODUCT(S) AND/OR THE PROGRAM(S) DESCRIBED
IN THIS WEB SITE AT ANY TIME.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
This section is extremely important. Please read it carefully.
IN NO EVENT SHALL WINCATALOG.COM, ORANGECAT SOFTWARE, LLC, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES,
CONTRACTORS, SUBCONTRACTORS, SUPPLIERS, AGENTS, AFFILIATES,
SUBSIDIARIES, SUCCESSORS OR ASSIGNS BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY
DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR OTHER INDIRECT (INCLUDING
WITHOUT LIMITATION, COST OF COVER) DAMAGES, LOSS OR INJURY ARISING OUT
OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS OF USE OR ANY SOFTWARE, SERVICES, DATA,
CONTENT OR OTHER MATERIALS PROVIDED OR AVAILABLE HEREUNDER, OR USE
OF ANY OTHER LINKS OR LINKED WEBSITE, EVEN IF WE ARE EXPRESSLY ADVISED
OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, AND REGARDLESS OR WHETHER SUCH
DAMAGES ARISE IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION
NEGLIGENCE), STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHER LEGAL BASIS NOW OR HEREAFTER
KNOWN. THE TERM “DAMAGES” INCLUDES, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ATTORNEYS FEES,
LOST PROFITS, PHYSICAL AND/OR PERSONAL INJURY, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION,
AND LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON YOUR INFORMATION HANDLING
SYSTEM. THE USER AGREES AND ACKNOWLEDGES THE ECONOMIC TERMS OF
THESE TERMS OF USE FAIRLY AND EQUITABLY REFLECT THE FOREGOING
ALLOCATION OF RISK AND SUCH ALLOCATION OF RISK IS A MATERIAL INDUCEMENT
FOR WINCATALOG.COM OR ORANGECAT SOFTWARE, LLC TO MAKE AVAILABLE TO THE
USER ITS SERVICES, WEBSITE AND OTHER CONTENT AND MATERIALS.
Cookie Policy
General information about cookies
Like most websites, WinCatalog.com uses cookies and web log files to track site usage.
Cookies are small files that are sent to and stored on your computer by the websites you visit. Cookies are stored in your browser’s file directory. Next time you visit the site, your browser will read the cookie and relay the information back to the website or element that originally set the cookie.
Cookies cannot damage your computer or the files stored on your computer.
You can adjust your browser so that you don’t receive any cookies during your next visit of the web site. In order to know more about these functions you can consult the Help function of your browser.
How WinCatalog.com uses cookies
This website stores cookies on your computer. These cookies are used to collect information about how you interact with our website and allow us to remember you.
We use this information in order to improve and customize your browsing experience and for analytics and metrics about our visitors on this website.
We use this information anonymously and do not know anything about you except the pages you visited on our site, where have you come from to our site, and some technical parameters that do not contain personal information. Please read more about the information we collect below in the Privacy Policy section.
Privacy Policy
We recognize and value our customers' privacy.
We commit to ensure that customers are informed how their personal information will be used and kept secure.
This privacy policy applies to information collected by WinCatalog.com through the websites,
products and services that display this privacy policy, including products and services
that may be provided by WinCatalog.com off-line.
This privacy policy applies to all WinCatalog.com products and services currently offered by WinCatalog.com.
The information collected and processed by WinCatalog.com
Communications from you. When you email or write to us, you may provide us with your name, contact details, and other personal
information in your message.
Order information. To purchase the Software you must make an order on one of our the partner websites.
All provided information will be processed according to our partner privacy policy. From our partners we get your name, email address
together with your IP-address, and in some cases your address. We do not get from our partners credit card information or any other private
financial information.
Automatically generated information. WinCatalog.com collects automatically generated information about your behavior during
your use of the web site. This information consists for instance of your IP-address, resolution of the screen, operating system, last visits,
times of visits, in order to recognize you, to customize your experience, to maintain and improve the web site and to serve advertisements. A
part of this information is collected with a help of Google Analytics (a free web analytics service provided by Google) which is also used
by us in order to enchase and improve our website.
Cookies. Like most websites, WinCatalog.com uses cookies and web log files to track site usage.
A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer which allows the web site to recognize you as a User when you return to the web site
using the same computer and browser. Cookies cannot damage your computer or the files stored on your computer.
You can adjust your browser so that you don’t receive any cookies during your next visit of the web site.
In order to know more about these functions you can consult the Help function of your browser.
Testimonials. When you explicitly send a testimonial via the Rate App functionality, we can use the text you sent and your name
to publish your feedback and your rating on our websisite in the testimonials section. We reserve a right to translate
testimonials sent in other language than English. We may contact back to you using the email address you provided, but your email address will never
be published on our website and in any form will never be passed to any 3rd party company.
Purposes for which WinCatalog.com uses personal data
WinCatalog.com uses your personal data for the following purposes:
To manage your product registration: we require your name and email address to generate and send or re-send you a registration code.
To send you service or promotional communication (we may use your personal information to send you newsletters that provide you with articles and information that we believe may be of interest to you).
To inform you about relevant information and developments within the web site or software.
To analyze data within the web site with the purpose of improving and/or customizing the web site.
Changes to the privacy policy
We are always looking for ways to improve our business and our practices. Consequently, our policies will continue to evolve.
As such, WinCatalog.com reserves the right to alter this privacy policy from time to time. Changes to this policy will be posted
to our WinCatalog.com website.
